<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PeddyPraxis</string>
    <string name="preambPatio"> Freshers are usually shy … \n The purpose of the first task is to put the freshman in the right frame of mind to face the challenges ahead! \n Freshman, for goodness sake, head out to the patio in front of the bar of Building A!
    \n\n Task: The freshman has to walk, for 5 minutes in a row, around the courtyard of the ed. A, blinking an eye and smiling with the front camera of the mobile device pointed at you </string>
    <string name="patio"> The Courtyard </string>
    <string name="preambEdificios"> Campus 2 has several buildings, each one identified by a letter (A, B, C, D). Some have been studying for several years at IPL and have difficulty remembering the letter that identifies a particular building. Caloiro, for your convenience, go to the roundabout at the entrance to Ed. A! Task: The freshman has to take a picture of the letter that identifies each of the four buildings. </string>
    <string name="edificios"> The Buildings </string>
    <string name="biblioteca"> The Library </string>
    <string name="preamBiblioteca"> The José Saramago Library is perhaps the most emblematic of Campus 2 buildings. Any self-respecting e-Godfather should motivate his freshman to acclimatize to this temple of knowledge. Caloiro, Please, go to the Library!  \n \nTest: The José Saramago Library is an area of ​​Culture, Knowledge and …? </string>
    <string name="descompressap"> Decompression </string>
    <string name="preambDescompressao">Being familiar is a lot of fun, but in the end you have to go back to the real world … \n The freshman should carry out an outdoor meditation session that allows him to relax so that you can go back to class calmly and concentratively. \nColour, for your convenience, head out to the patio in front of the bar of Building A! \n \nTest: The freshman must be seated for 10 minutes, in the courtyard of the ed. A, with the phone on your lap with the screen facing down (it s for relaxing!). If it is raining the freshman can fulfill this task in one of the 3 points of interest nearest the place where it is.</string>
    <string name="prembuloEdificios"> Campus 2 has several buildings, each one identified by a letter (A, B, C, D). \nThere are many years of studying (or working …) in the IPL and have difficulty remembering the letter that identifies a particular building. \nCalendar, please, go to the roundabout at the entrance to Ed. A! \n \nTest: The freshman has to go to all the buildings and confirm that he is near them when showing with the camera "Building X" </string>
    <string name="imHere"> I\'m here! </string>
    <string name="RegSuc"> Resected successfully </string>
        
    <string name="RegFail"> Failed registration: </string>
    <string name="EmpPass"> User password can not be empty </string>    
    <string name="empEmail"> User email can not be empty </string>   
    <string name="enterAllFields"> Please enter all fields </string>  
    <string name="loginIN"> Log in! </string>
    <string name="logFail"> Failed login </string>
    <string name="logSuc"> Session started successfully </string> 
    <string name="errLerDados"> Error trying to save user data </string> 
    <string name="gameTitle"> PeddyPraxis </string> 
    <string name="descrGame"> Best Ever Game </string>
    <string name="gameAuth"> <![CDATA[Parracho & Xavi]]> </string>  
    <string name="estatiTitle"> Statistics </string>
    <string name="name"> Name: </string>
    <string name="age"> Age: </string>
    <string name="bestTime"> Best time: </string> 
    <string name="numGameStr"> Number of games performed: </string>
    <string name="finishGame"> Number of completed games: </string>
    <string name="percVict"> Percentage of victories: </string>
    <string name="qstnLog"> Do you really want to sign out of your account? </string>
    <string name="lestPlay"> So let\'s continue playing! </string>
    <string name="enterMail"> Please enter your registered email ID </string>
    <string name="sndEmail"> Sending Email! </string>

    <string name="passResSnt"> Email with reset password sent </string>
        
    <string name="errEmailRstPass"> Error sending password reset email </string>
        
    <string name="run"> Run </string>
        
    <string name="runDesc"> The freshman has 30 seconds to move to the esslei. Start in the courtyard of A. </string>
        
    <string name="fnsGame1h"> Good Freshman! You managed to complete everything in 1 hour even by little </string>
        
    <string name="fnshGameInTime"> Good Freshman! You have completed everything in </string>
        
    <string name="min"> minutes and </string>
        
    <string name="sec"> seconds </string>
        
    <string name="finTime"> Unfortunately the time is up! You just completed </string>
        
    <string name="numTask"> number of tasks </string>
        
    <string name="returnGmMn"> Back Game Menu </string>
        
    <string name="goPatA"> Freshman head for the courtyard of A </string>
        
    <string name="goRotA"> Freshman go to the roundabout near the A </string>
        
    <string name="goBib"> Freshman head to the Library </string>
        
    <string name="rightAns"> Enter the correct answer! </string>
        
    <string name="extGame"> Exit Game </string>
        
    <string name="retMnJg"> Does freshman want to return to the game menu? </string>
        
    <string name="warnLst"> Freshman is sure to finish the game! Any progress you\'ve made will be lost </string>
        
    <string name="fngame"> End Game </string>
        
    <string name="cancel"> Cancel </string>
        
    <string name="congt"> PARABENS! </string>
        
    <string name="checksta"> Good freshman! You managed to improve your time, congratulations! Check the information icon to see your stats </string>
        
    <string name="descPat"> The freshman has to walk, for 5 minutes in a row, around the yard ed. A, blinking an eye and smiling with the front camera of the mobile device pointed at you! </string>
        
    <string name="endTask"> Exit Task </string>
        
    <string name="Bibl"> The Library </string>
        
    <string name="descBib"> The José Saramago Library is an area of ​​Culture, Knowledge and ...? To complete this task, you should take a photo of the answer somewhere in the Library </string>
        
    <string name="finish"> End </string>
        
    <string name="descomp"> Decompression </string>
        
    <string name="descompDesc"> The freshman must be seated for 10 minutes in the courtyard of the ed. A, with the phone on your lap with the screen facing down (it\'s for relaxing!). </string>
        
    <string name="atention"> Attention! </string>
        
    <string name="warnAtent"> It has been detected that the best conditions are not met to finish this activity in the yard. </string>
        
    <string name="goNearbyPlac"> Please go to one of these places of interest if you wish. </string>
        
    <string name="descCorrida"> Freshman is sure you want to leave! Any progress you\'ve made will be lost </string>
</resources>
